brevardschools.org 2013-10-04

# Web Disclaimer Statement

Disclaimer, Security Statement, Privacy Statement, and External Link Statement

**Disclaimer**  
The information and data on this site is dynamic and will change over time. We strive to provide current and accurate information; however, the information and materials provided on this site should not be relied upon exclusively. 

**Security Statement**  
Access to personal information about you is limited to individuals authorized by law to have access to that information.  
Physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards are in place to protect personal information.  
When confidential information is involved, industry-standard encryption is in use to protect data.

**Privacy Statement**  
Any personal information requested or gathered via this site will be used only for purposes necessary to conduct government business with you. It will not be traded, sold, or given to any other party except as specifically allowed or required by law. We cannot guarantee the privacy and confidentiality of information provided to us via this site.

**Link Statement**  
In the course of providing the best service to the public, Brevard County Schools may link to other organizations to provide additional useful information for our customers. These include: 

  1. Links to a site owned by the federal government, a state government, or a local government 
  2. Links to educational or non-profit organizations that complement the information or services offered by Brevard Public Schools
  3. Links to a Web site owned by an entity that has a business or contractual relationship with Brevard Public Schools

No endorsement is intended or made of any link, product, service, or information either by its inclusion or exclusion on this site. We do not control or guarantee the accuracy, relevance, timeliness or completeness of this outside information. If you access another site through a link we provide, you are subject to the privacy policy of that site.
